day on the ideal vacation of an Uzbek girl in America.  I woke up at 8:05 in the morning, got dressed, and
went straight to the gym.  I
left the gym at 10:05 and drank a tropical smoothie.   It was
so delicious.  Then
I came to my senses because I was hungry as usual
.  And for Nas, show me my favorite kubnika
.  I lovingly
cut our kubnikas and spread our kara chezez on our toasted bread and
ate them with relish
.  Then I sat down to teach, saying Bismillah
.  Whatever class you ask for in the summer
, I have tutoring classes in chemistry and biology
.  About four
hours later, I got ready again, went
outside, and
went to Target.
I returned home feeling happy.  When I get older, my mother and
sister.  They were
preparing it for dinner.  I also
changed my clothes and
made a salad.  After dinner,
we watched a movie, and then I did my homework,
read a little, and went to sleep.  If you
watched the video to the end, please
answer this question.  Sweetie
pie.  Com.